puzzlewarehouse.com 2019-11-15

# Privacy Policy | PuzzleWarehouse.com

### **_We care about transparency. Some websites hide their practices from their customers and visitors. We prefer honesty._**

As online shoppers ourselves, relevant and personalized ads or emails are always more interesting than irrelevant ads or emails. In order to power relevant, interest-based content and advertisements for you, we need partners to help us identify you when you interact with us. Our partners may collect non-personal information like your IP address, device ID, shopping behavior, and information about your browser or operating system. We may share information about you such as your email or other identifiers with our partners. If we do, we always share it in a non-human-readable form to ensure the security of your information. Our partners may combine our personal and non-personal information about you with information from other sources, and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser, all to help us communicate better with you.

We also care about choice. You can opt-out of these services at any time. To opt-out of BouncePilot’s services, please go to [http://BouncePilot.com/opt-out/](http://bouncepilot.com/opt-out/). To opt out of LiveRamp’s services, please go to <http://www.liveramp.com/opt_out>. To opt-out of third party cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. To opt-out of the use of your mobile device ID for targeted advertising, please see <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>.

###  ** _Safe Shopping Guarantee_**

The Puzzle Warehouse Safe Shopping Guarantee protects you while you shop at Puzzle Warehouse so that you never have to worry about credit card safety. Period.

We guarantee that every transaction you make at Puzzle Warehouse will be safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at Puzzle Warehouse. See guarantee details below.

###  ** _Why is Puzzle Warehouse so safe?_**

  * Safety in Numbers: When you shop at Puzzle Warehouse, you'll be one of the thousands of customers who have safely shopped with us without credit card fraud.
  * Safe Technology: Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is provided by Google, one of the world's leading providers of Internet trust services and we believe it is the best software available today for secure online commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. You can rest assured that your personal information is safe.

###  ** _You still don't want to use your credit card on the Internet?_**

No problem. Just call our toll-free number at 1-866-539-4278 and one of our outstanding customer service representatives will be glad to take your order.

###  ** _Guarantee Details:_**

  1. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50, Puzzle Warehouse will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50. Puzzle Warehouse will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at Puzzle Warehouse while using the secure server.
  2. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

Copyright © 2008-2019, Puzzle Warehouse, All rights reserved.

Puzzle Warehouse recycles everything it can to save the environment and to keep costs and prices low.

We are Hiring! Please fill out the [employment form](http://www.puzzlewarehouse.com/employment-form/) or send your resume to [Career@waytechnology.com](mailto:Career@waytechnology.com).
